<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EchoNotes</string>
    <string name="news_content">Superficially, Wasteland 3\'s turn-based combat looks a lot like Wasteland 2\'s (or XCOM\'s, for that matter), and its emphasis on action points and flanking doesn\'t differ much from familiar tactical RPGs.\n\n A few changes, though, make it a heck of a lot more satisfying this time around. For one thing, the key change is that enemies and friendlies take turns as an entire team. Within a team, though, you\'re free to choose which order your characters fire in, even to the point of hopping back to a specific character after you\'ve spent all the action points for another. This can be brutally punishing if you didn\'t get your squad members set behind cover before the fight begins and the entire enemy team gets a free shot, but it also means you can use your heavy hitters when you absolutely need them most. There\'s also a greater emphasis on environmental interaction this time around, ranging from simply blowing up explosive barrels to firing the big gun mounted on top of the Kodiak.\n\n It\'s especially satisfying to unleash precision attack abilities by building the strike meter after a few rounds of normal attacks, as these can turn the tide in seemingly hopeless battle\n\nAnd there are many such battles. Wasteland 3 is as tough as its Rangers, and it\'s overly fond of tossing you into overwhelming situations with little easy access to cover. It rewards careful thinking, though, such as making you find terminals that shut down deadly weapons or remember to bring along a few deployable turrets of your own for extra protection. Cool weapons spice it up, too, such as the Frozen Ferret Launcher (which is exactly what it sounds like). It\'s also relatively easy to revive downed team members, so total wipeouts weren\'t as common as I expected them to be when I was first learning the ropes of combat. When I needed an extra health boost in combat, the new shared inventory made it easier to find one.
    </string>
</resources>